freearticlesandcontent.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy Policy | Free Stuff for Your Brain

**Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Like most websites, Our Website collects non-personally identifiable information from visitors of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available. Visitors to Our Website website who have javascript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects the following non-personally identifiable types of information from users:

  * Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number
  * Type of operating system
  * Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen)
  * Javascript support
  * Flash version
  * Screen resolution
  * Time of visit
  * Pages visited
  * Time spent on each page of the website
  * Referring site statistics 
    * The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website)
    * Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine)

This data is primarily used by Our Website for internal use in order to optimize Our Website website for visitors, however Our Website will use this data for marketing purposes. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to Our Website website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website.

As previously mentioned, Our Website, via Google Analytics, also collects potentially personally identifiable information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Our Website does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifiable information, as described below.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

Certain visitors to Our Website website choose to interact with Our Website in ways that require Our Website to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Our Website gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. These interactions include but are not limited to the collection of:

  * Names and email addresses for visitors who leave comments via the comment system
  * Email addresses for visitors who opt to receive email notification when posts and comments are published

In each case, Our Website collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Our Website. Our Website does not disclose personally identifiable information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Protection of Certain Personally Identifiable Information**

Our Website discloses potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Our Website’s behalf or to provide services available at Our Website’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Our Website’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Our Website will not rent or sell potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Our Website discloses potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information only when required to do so by law, or when Our Website believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Our Website, third parties, or the public at large.

**Third Party Advertising**

Our Website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Our Website website. These companies, including Google, may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google uses what is called a [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) for this purpose. If you would like to opt out of Google’s DART program, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Our Website uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of Our Website website, and their website access preferences. Our Website visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Our Website’s website, with the drawback that certain features of Our Website’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Our Website may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Our Website’s sole discretion. Our Website encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
